Hello.
こんにちは
Nice to meet you.
初めましてですね
Where is this?
ここはどこですか?
Love Otel.
ラヴオーテル
La Vautel.
ラ ヴオーテル
Do you know what I'm doing today?
今日何してるかって知ってます?
What are you doing?
何してるんですか?
It was really good.
めっちゃ良かった
Are you relieved?
安心しました?
It was conveyed properly.
ちゃんと伝わってて
I'm going to record a naughty video.
エ ッチなビデオ撮っちゃいます
We will release it worldwide.
全世界で公開しちゃいます
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
That's cute.
それ可愛らしいですね
Do you like Shiro?
シロが好きなんですか?
like...
好き...
Oh, don't you like it?
あ、好きじゃないの?
It's all white though.
全身真っ白だけど
It becomes a lot.
多くなっちゃう
Will there be more?
多くなっちゃうの?
Don't you like that?
それ好きなんじゃないの?
It's cute.
可愛いですね
What do you want to call it?
何と呼びしたいですか?
Please don't use your real name.
本名はやめてね
Who do you say you look like?
誰に似てるって言われます?
cute.
可愛い
Cute Irina-chan?
可愛 いりなちゃん?
It was a while ago.
なんか少し昔だよね
Do you know?
知ってるの?
I don't know.
知ってないです
Oh, really?
あ、ガチ?
Seriously?
マジ?
Oh, how old are you?
お、いくつですか?
It's cute.
可愛いね
They look similar.
似てるね
Certainly.
確かにね
Your feet don't smell bad.
足は臭くないですよね
I'm sorry.
すみませんね
Even if someone doesn't do it.
誰かしなくても
Ah, so cute.
あ、可愛い
It's going to rain at home today.
今日雨で家になっちゃうね
Yes, it's raining a lot.
はい、めっちゃ降ってます
So cute.
すごい可愛い
Please stand up.
立ってごらん
How many centimeters tall are you?
身長何センチですか?
155?
155か
That's amazing.
すごいね
148 cm.
148センチ
What is it? Did you want to be taller?
それは何か、もっと身長が欲しかった?
I wanted it for a long time.
長く欲しかった
Did you want it?
欲しかったの?
But it's delicate.
でも、華奢ですよ
It's crunchy.
カリカリですね
Crunchy?
カリカリ?
Do you like any idols?
何かアイドルとか好きなのですか?
Maumus.
モウムス
Do you like Moumus?
モウムス好きなの?
That's old.
古いね
It's all old.
全部古いね
Moumus and others are from my uncle's generation.
モウムスとか、おじさん世代だよ
Wasn't Moums the old ladies right now?
モウムスって、今、 おばさん達じゃなかったっけ?
Are there any young Moumus?
若いモウムスもあるの?
Graduated.
卒業して
Graduation pattern?
卒業パターン?
Is that what you mean?
そういうことなの?
Didn't know?
知りませんでした?
It's a Moumus that I don't know.
知らないモウムスなんだね
is that so.
そうですか
yes.
はい
So, can I call you Rina-chan today?
じゃあ、今日リナちゃんって呼んでいい?
Because Lina is cute.
かわいいリナだから
It's okay, right?
大丈夫だよね?
Ah, Rina-chan is cute.
あ、リナちゃんかわいい
Can I look at you like I'm licking you?
舐めるように見ていい?
The socks are cute too.
靴下もかわいらしいですね
Can I look inside the forbidden area?
禁断の中見ていいですか?
May I?
いいですか?
You're so kind.
優しいね
Spread your legs a little more
足広げで、もうちょっと
He's molesting me.
痴 漢してるんですよ
痴 漢?
Have you ever experienced molestation?
痴漢咲いたことありますか?
Oh, is there?
あ、あるの?
What are you going to do?
どうするんですか?
I'll chase you.
追 いかけます
It's active.
活発だね
Are you chasing me?
追いかけるの?
Do you like Izuni?
いずに好きですか?
Actually, I don't know much about it.
実に、あんまり知らないんです
Don't you know?
知らないの?
If a pervert blooms, I'll go after it.
痴漢咲いたら追いかけるんだ
I'll chase you
追いかけます
hey.
ね
She's a strong woman.
強 い女性ですね
Turn around for a moment and touch the sofa.
ちょっと後ろを向いて、 ソファに手ついて 手ついてまいるから
Stick your butt out First, stick out your butt.
お 尻突き出して まずお尻突き出してください
Take Ina's butt.
イナちゃんのお尻を取ります
Please roll up your skirt.
スカートまくり上げてください
Please pull your pants down.
パンツをガッツリ伏せください
Gently.
ガッツリ
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしいの?
Oh la la la la la, you like white, right?
あらららららら 白好きでしょ?
The pants are also white.
パンツも白ですよ
Can I sit down?
座っていい?
You're sitting here like this, you pervert.
こうやって座ってくるんでしょ、痴漢は
I'm sorry.
す みませんね
Please stand here, facing forward.
そのままこっち、正面向いて立ってください
Please stand normally.
普通に立ってください
Please show me your pants.
パンツ見せてください
Can it be expanded further?
もっと広げられる?
Well then, Ina-chan.
じゃあ、イナちゃん
Let's take one step closer to the way we were born.
一歩、生まれた姿に 生まれたての姿に近づけましょう
Let's take off your top clothes.
上の服脱ぎましょう
Well, let's take it all off.
そうや、全部脱いじゃいましょう
It seems difficult to cut it alone.
一人で切るの大変そうだね
That's what happened.
そうなってたんだ
I won't remove it yet.
それはまだ抜かないね
Put your hair back.
髪の毛後ろにして
Oh, that's nice.
おー、ナイスバリーですね
Are you eating rice?
ご飯食べてます?
Are you eating?
食べてます?
I'll take the thumbnail.
サムネとるよ
Please turn back.
後ろ向いてください
Show me your butt.
お尻見せて
Please look forward.
前向いてください
There's a chandelier coming from my belly button.
なんかおへそからシャンデリアが
Didn't this hurt?
これ痛くなかったの?
It didn't hurt.
痛くなかった
Really?
本当に?
Doesn't it hurt?
痛くないの?
I'll have it done.
マスイしてもらう
Did you miss it?
マスイしたの?
Masui hurts.
マスイが痛い
Those are beautiful breasts.
綺麗なおっぱいですね
So cute, Lina.
かわいい、リナちゃん
I wonder if I'm showing my face like this?
こんな顔出してるかな?
What do you think?
どうだろう?
That's great.
どうもいいね
Just go to bed.
ちょっとベッド行って
Do you remember the pose you did when you first took the thumbnail in bed?
ベッドで最初サムネとった時のポーズ覚えてる?
Put your hair back.
髪の毛後ろにして
Oh yeah, nice.
そうそう、いいね
It's really good.
すごい良いですよ
Would this be good?
こっちもいいかな?
Bring your hands behind your head.
両手を頭の後ろに持ってきてください
Good luck and good luck.
頑張って頑張って
It's a bit painful, isn't it?
ちょっと辛いよね
Rounded sides.
脇が丸め
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Check.
確認します
Is it in?
入ってる?
They don't come into my house.
うちに入らないんですよ
Yeah.
うん
There's only one in there though.
1本だけ入ってるけど
Awkward.
気まずい
I don't like it.
嫌だ
Hate, hate, hate, hate.
嫌い嫌い嫌い嫌い嫌い
Is it awkward?
気まずいの?
I don't go in, so I don't watch it.
入らないから、見ないんですよ
But it's easy.
でも楽だね
I got one.
1本入りました
I think it's my imagination too.
僕の気もせいだと思います
Kushiwai.
くしわい
Come around here for a moment.
ちょっとこっち回ってきて
Fix your hair.
髪の毛を修正して
To get closer to the person you were born with
生まれた姿に近づくため
To.
に
Ji Ross.
ジ ロスね
Giros.
ジロスね
I could see a little bit of his neck.
ちょっと口首見えた
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしいの?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Be brave.
勇気を出して
Quickly.
パッと
Hello.
こんにちは
It's beautiful.
綺麗ですね
Fix your hair and wait.
髪の毛を修正して待って
I'll sleep in the morning.
朝寝とるね
It's a pain, but go back to your bed.
めんどくさいんですけど、またそっちのベッドに行って
I want to see Mina's beautiful figure.
みなちゃんの綺麗な姿を取りたい
Should I be careful?
気をつけしようか
Where is your body's best point?
自分の体のチャンポイントはどこですか?
Bring your hands under your head.
両手を頭の下に持ってきて
Are you satisfied with your current breasts?
今のおっぱいで満足してる?
Yeah.
うん
Is it just the right size?
ちょうど良い大きさ?
Just right.
ちょうどいい
It's tough, isn't it?
きついよね
You can avoid it now.
もう避けていいよ
Come here.
こっち来て
Then, can I lick Mina's breasts?
じゃあみなちゃんのおっぱい舐めていいですか?
good?
いい?
It's close to my clothes, so I can put them there.
服とかが近いから、そっちの方に置けるから
I'll set up the camera.
カメラをセッティングしますよ
What is your favorite food?
好きな食べ物は何ですか?
Udon.
うどん
Udon?
うどん?
Do you like Hanuki udon?
はぬきうどんが好きですか?
Now...
今には...
Is it really that guy?
やっぱかーやつ?
Hoho guy?
ほほーやつ?
That's right.
そうなんですよ
Don't you like thin ramen noodles?
ラーメンの細麺とかは好きじゃない?
I like it lightly.
あっさりがいいんだね
Please sit down.
座ってください
Shine your hair.
髪の毛をシャインして
Everyone, please excuse my neighbor.
み なさん、お隣に失礼します
Why are you showing your eyes through the wall of your mouth?
口の壁なんでお目出ししてるの?
I like it.
好きなの
Oh, really?
あ、そう?
It smells amazing.
すごい匂いする
Really?
ほんとに?
It smells delicious.
うまい匂いする
Isn't it?
じゃねーですか?
Please be honest.
正直に言ってください
What smell is this?
何の匂いこれ?
It smells amazing.
すごい匂いする
It doesn't smell at all.
全然匂わない
全然匂わないです
That's cute, but not everyone.
可愛いえ、みなさんではないね
I was surprised.
びっくりしたね
Is it fashionable?
おしゃれですか?
Have you ever smelled something?
匂い叩いたことありますか?
I had to let them know.
伝えてもらっちゃいました
Please push up with both hands.
両手押し上げてください
That's difficult.
難しいね
Please look at the camera.
カメラ見てください
That's amazing.
すごいね
You're sensitive.
敏感だね
Check the sides.
脇をチェックしてください
Hold the back of your head with your right hand.
右手だけ頭の後ろを持ってください
picture?
え?
It smells amazing.
すごい匂いします
Is rock pero ok?
ロックペロロックペロでいいですか?
May I?
いいですか?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
I think my arms are tight.
腕がきついと思うんだけど
That's not it.
そんなじゃん
what?
何ですか?
Contains pepper.
コショウが入ってます
You can put down the pepper.
コショウを下ろしていいよ
I'll also put my hair back.
髪の毛も後ろに入れていくから
Not at all, right?
全然じゃないですか
Please wash it carefully afterwards.
後で念入りに洗っておいてください
Uncle's spit stinks.
おじさんのツバは臭いですよ
Shall I take off my last remaining panties?
最後残っているパンツを脱ぎましょうか
Can I wait a moment?
ちょっと待っていい?
Now let's take it off.
じゃあ脱ぎましょう
Yes, stop.
はい、ストップ
I don't like it.
嫌だ
picture?
え?
Check your pants for stains.
パンツのシミをチェックします
I don't like it, I don't like it.
嫌だ嫌だ
I really don't like it.
本当に嫌だ
Well then, you can hide what's wrong with you.
じゃあ、やばいところを隠していいよ
Dangerous place?
やばいところ?
No, isn't it dangerous?
いや、やばくないの?
Then, you can hide the parts you don't want to move to the wall.
じゃあ、どうしても壁に移したくないところは隠していいよ
I really don't want to move everything.
どうしても全部移したくない
It's okay, absolutely.
大丈夫だよ、全然
No.
ダメだよ
It's just fabric.
ただの生地ですよ
It's no good anymore.
もうダメだよ
Ah, okay.
あ、オッケー
I want you to turn it inside out.
裏返しにしてほしいのよ
Turn it inside out and hide only the bad parts.
裏返しにして、 やばいところだけ隠してください
You can make it a little parallel.
ちょっと平行にできる
Ah, yes, that's nice.
あ、 そうそう、いいね
Are there roots here?
ここの根があるのか
No.
ダメ
Because it's on the butt side?
だってお尻側だっけ?
It's not a butt root.
お尻の根じゃない
Is that your crotch side?
そっちはお股側?
Crotch side.
お股側
Not on the crotch side
お 股側いない
mosquito.
か
amazing hard
すごい 硬
stomach.
い
Is it okay to use a talker?
ト ーカーでもダメ?
No.
ダメ
Well, bring it to the side of your face.
じゃあ、顔の横持ってきて
Did it get stained?
染みつけちゃったの?
yes.
はい
I was walking around with it stained.
染みつけて歩いてましたって
I'm sorry for staining it.
染みつけてすいませんって
Sorry for staining it.
染みつけてすいません
I've been walking around with it stained.
染みつけて歩いてきましたって
Go ahead.
いってこな
I walked away soaking it in.
染みつけて歩いてきました
It's ingrained in everyone.
みんな染みつけてますからね
Yes, please turn back.
はい、じゃあ背戻してください
Then I'll take the whole body.
じゃあちょっと全身取りますよ
It has hair in it.
お毛毛が入ってる
picture?
え?
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしいの?
Someone with his hand on his butt
ちょっとお尻に手乗ってる人
Is it cutting?
が 切ってるの?
I'm cutting it.
切ってます
Are you ready?
揃えてるの?
It's arranged neatly.
綺麗に揃えてるね
The hair is straight.
まっすぐなんですよね、毛が
Oh, is that so?
あ、そうなの?
After all, you have to keep spinning.
や っぱ り、 クルクルしてなくちゃ
Hey, ah, is that so?
へー、あ、そうなの?
It's so fluffy.
モジャモジャだね
Why don't you just cut off one leg?
ちょっと足一本切ってごらん?
Would you like to cut one more?
もっと一本切ってごらん?
Good, good.
いいね、いいね
It's amazing looking.
すごい見てる
Be careful.
気をつけして
Take it to your butt.
お尻に持ってって
I've already taken 30 minutes.
もう30分を取ってるよ
Rina-chan's body alone has that much potential.
りなちゃんの 体だけで、それぐらいポテンシャルありますよ
I have drawing skills.
絵力があります
So, should I turn around?
じゃあ、後ろ向けるかな?
I'll take your butt.
お尻取るね
Do you understand the M-shaped reform?
M字改革って分かりますか?
Finally, do the M-shape reform on the sofa.
ソファーで最後にM字改革してください
Salt your hair
髪の毛を塩にして、
Bring your hands behind your head.
両 手、頭の後ろに持ってきてください
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
I'll take a photo.
写真撮りますよ
Why are your legs closed?
なんで足閉じてるの?
Even with your legs closed, you can see everything.
足閉じても まる見えですよ
Would you like to spread your legs?
足広げてごらん?
It's too much, and I'm disappointed.
余計して、ガッと
Ma-chan, can you spread it out?
まーちゃん、広げれる?
Ah, nice.
あ、いいね
Well then, let's take a bath.
じゃあ、お風呂入ろっか
Thank you for your continued support today.
今日よろしくお願いしますね
please.
お願いします
That's fun.
楽しいの、それ
Well then, let's continue.
じゃあ、続きとるよ
Did you wash it properly?
綺麗に洗った?
Washed well.
綺麗に洗った
Did you wash it?
洗った?
洗っちゃったの?
I washed it.
洗ったよ
I added a scent.
匂いをつけたのに
Macking.
マッキング
Now, take a towel and look at Rina-chan's skin-like face.
じゃあ、タオル取って、 肌カンボの りなちゃんの肌顔をね
That way, you can do the pose you just did.
そっち、さっきのポーズできるから
Isn't it processed?
加工してないの?
It becomes a beautiful volley line that looks like it has been processed.
加工したみたいにすごい 綺麗なボリーラインになるね
That's amazing.
すごいね
And put your hands behind your head.
で、両手を 頭の後ろに
Yes, let's do our best to expose everything openly.
そう、精々堂々と すべてをさらけ出そう
Bring it back again.
もう一回、後ろに持って行って
Let's expose everything.
すべてをさらけ出そう
Well then, finally roll over.
じゃあさ、ついに転がって
This one is good.
こっちがいいね
I'll flirt with you a little.
ちょっとイチャイチャしますよ
what happened?
どうしたの?
come.
来る
cold?
寒い?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
You can cut it.
切ってもいいよ
That's why.
そっからでしょ
My friend is acting like a dentist on the other side of the glitter.
お友達が ラメの向こうで 歯医師のようにしてるから
I'll ask the dentist to do it for me.
私で 歯医師でしてって言ってもらおう
It took two people.
2人かけたんで
It's time for a little more sleep.
もうちょっと おやすみだよ
Yeah.
うん
Design smell?
設計の匂い?
Can I lick your tongue?
舌舐めちゃっていい?
Be conscious of the men on the other side of the camera.
カメラの向こうにいる 男たちを意識して
Close to your mangoes.
みなさんのマンゴー近くへ
It's so beautiful.
すごい綺麗だね
I'll expand it a little.
ちょっと広げるよ
It's still small.
まだちっちゃいね
I saw it, I saw it, I saw it.
見えた見えた見えた
Doesn't it hurt?
痛くない?
My knees are full.
膝がいっぱいだね
A mango that looks pleasant.
気持ちよさそうな マンゴー
I'll go eat some food too.
食いとりするのもいくよ
It's so small to eat it.
食いとりするのちっちゃいね
It's small.
ちっちゃいね
You don't know it yourself.
自分ではわからないよね
Don't you compare girls with each other?
女の子同士見比べっこしないの?
I won't.
しないよ
It's short.
短いね
Doesn't it hurt?
痛くない?
Hello.
こんにちは
Did you leave?
いっちゃったの?
Did it feel good?
気持ちよかった?
This person is difficult to kiss, right?
この人はキスするの大変でしょ?
Isn't it hard to kiss your boyfriend?
彼氏とキスするの大変でしょ?
Did it feel good?
気持ちよかった?
Would you like to go nearby?
近くに行きたいと思う?
get closer to the camera
カメラに近づけるの
mosquito?
か?
Looks like I'm a really big guy.
俺 がすごい大きな男みたいだな
I don't like it, I don't like it.
嫌だ嫌だね
I was confused.
迷いがあったね
I hate my boyfriend more than doing this.
こんなことするよりも彼氏が嫌だね
Is it okay for my boyfriend to do this?
彼氏がこんなことしちゃっていいの?
I don't like that person at all.
その人全然嫌だね
This is dangerous.
これはやばいですよ
Uri-san, please reward me generously.
うりさん、いっぱいご報酬してください
I don't like it.
嫌だよ
嫌だ
Just a little more.
もうちょいもうちょい
Come here and do whatever you want.
こっちに来て何でもいい
Well then?
さては?
What can I bring closer?
近づけるのは?
Let it escape?
逃がす?
I don't like white panties. They're white pants like Ina-chan.
白パンチ 嫌 イナちゃんと同じ白パンツだよ
It's true.
本当だ
It's matching.
おそろいだ
They all match.
お そろいだよ
I got scared.
ビビになっちゃったな
cute?
可愛い?
cute.
可愛い
Are you cute today?
今日は可愛い?
Did you get scared?
ビビになっちゃった?
Isn't it cute?
可愛くないかな
It's just cute.
可愛いだけくらいだよ
It's not cute.
可愛くない
Lick it.
舐めて
Not kind.
優しくない
It's like licking soft serve ice cream.
ソフトクリーム舐めるみたい
It's like licking a delicious vanilla soft serve.
美味しいバニラソフト舐めるみたい
No matter how I lick it.
どうしたら舐め上げても
Full of hair.
毛だらけ
I don't like it.
嫌だ
Lick me with a smile.
笑顔で舐めてくれ
Okay.
よし
Please take a selfie.
自撮りしててね
It's heavy.
重いよ
Is there an angle where you can leak?
自分の漏れる角度とかある?
I don't know.
わかんない
What is it?
どうなんだ?
How are you taking pictures?
どう撮れてるの?
It's heavy, isn't it?
重いよね
He's pale again.
また青白い
The light?
ライトが?
You can do it with brown light, though.
茶色いライトでもできるんだけどね
amazing.
すごい
You'll turn bright red.
真っ赤になっちゃうからね
copper?
どう?
Let me hear it.
聞かせてくれ
Should I help you?
手をつかわせばいい?
It feels amazing.
すごい気持ちいいよ
Is it cute?
可愛いですか?
It's not cute.
可愛くない
Like a harmonica suit.
ハーモニカ服みたいな
I don't like it.
私が嫌
Please look at the camera.
カメラ見てあげてね
Come to my sad house.
しょんぼりなお家に来い
It's good to come to a house where you're healthy.
元気なお家に来るのがいいでしょ
Can I take it in?
入れ取っていい?
Then go to sleep
じゃあ寝よっ
mosquito.
か
Let me tell you that I'm going to have sex with the old man.
俺 がおじさんとセックスしますって言ってもらおう
picture?
え?
I'm going to have sex with my uncle.
おじさんとセックスしますって
Please scold me.
叱ってください
You don't like having sex with your uncle?
おじさんとセックス嫌だ?
I don't like it.
嫌だ
Do you not like it?
嫌だの?
It can't be helped.
しょうがないね
it hurts?
痛い?
How many kilograms do you weigh?
体重何キロ?
30km.
30キロ
It's 30km.
30キロだよ
Seriously?
マジ?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Will you catch a cold?
風邪飛んでいっちゃうの?
I'll fly away.
飛んでくよ
You'll fly away in fear.
恐怖で飛んでくよね
Can I move it?
動かしていっていい?
Wait a little longer?
もうちょっと待つ?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
That's scary.
怖いな
It's like a dream.
夢のようだよ
I was able to do cute things and have sex.
可愛いことセックスできられて
Wait a minute?
ちょっと待ってる?
This is me.
これ、拙者ですよ
Do you want a thin boyfriend?
彼氏はやせてる人がいいの?
Pochon macho.
ポチョンマッチョ
Because something like this can't happen.
こんなやつありえないからね
Usually.
普通は
You don't want to be fat.
デブとやんないでしょ
You wouldn't let a fat person do it.
デブにはやらせないでしょ
cute.
可愛い
Do you want money?
お金欲しい?
want.
欲しい
Are you looking at me?
目でてくれてるの?
Are you cute?
可愛くてくれてる?
cute.
可愛い
cute?
可愛い?
Makeup, makeup.
化粧やろ、化粧
Will you move in?
振り入る?
That's a great posture.
凄い腰遣いだね
This is my first time.
これ初めてだ
An old man who came from hundreds of amateurs.
何百人という 素人でやってきたおじさん
This is amazing.
これ凄いわ
Where did you study?
どこで学んだの?
Brain child?
脳むす?
hate?
嫌う?
I wish I had an esthetician like this.
こんなエステマストーシーがあったらいいのに
There isn't.
無いな
Let's make an incision.
切開をしよう
You don't have to force yourself.
無理しなくていいよ
Are you going to continue to hang out with your uncle?
おじさんとおせく続くか
Because I want to have a beautiful face, yes.
綺麗な顔が取りたいから、 そう、
oh yeah.
そう、そう
Good, good.
いいね、いいね
I understand.
分かってるね
Now I can move.
これで俺が動くね
You've got some nasty pictures.
えげつな絵が取れてるよ
This is crazy.
これはヤバイ
Are your feet okay?
足大丈夫?
It may be difficult, but I can stand on my feet.
大変かもしれないけど、 足を立てれる
Do your best to stand on your feet.
足を頑張って立てよう
And just go back.
で、そのまま後ろに
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
そう、そう、そう、そう
Mr. Mori's shoulders seem to be stiff.
森さんの肩がつりそうです
I went in right away.
すぐすぐ入っちゃった
It's crazy, there's no limit.
ヤバイ、無限界だ
Dick's shoulder too.
チンコの肩も
That's crazy.
ヤバイ
This is disgusting.
えげつなね、これ
Okay, okay, okay.
よし、よし、よし
Take some more.
もうちょっと取って
Can you get out of the sexy heavy rotation?
セクスリーヘビーローテーションを抜けますか?
Yes, it will come out.
はい、抜けます
Can you open it and come out this way?
開いてこっちに抜ける?
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
そう、そう、そう、そう
Yes, nice, nice.
はい、いいね、いいね
Okay, okay.
よし、よし、
Okay.
よし
Hey, this pressure point is in there.
な あ、このツボツボ入ってる
It looks like a dick though.
チンコリっぽいんだけど
It's already at its limit.
もうそもそも限界だよね
Get out.
抜けて
OK、OK、OK
It looks like I'll be overtaken.
抜かれそうだ
Do you want me to remove it?
抜いてもらう?
Okay.
いいよ
Your arm hurts, right?
腕痛いでしょ?
Yeah, my arm hurts.
うん、腕痛い
I'll try a little harder to get it up, so
ちょっと頑張って立ててもらうので、
I wonder if I can bend over like that for a little while.
ちょっとしたら、そうやって、ひじついていいかな
oh yeah,
そう、そう、
yes.
そう
Would you like me to lend you a hand?
ちょっと 手を貸してもらう?
elbow
ひじ
You can follow me now.
つ いていいよ、もう
Yeah.
うん
It's smooth.
すべすべだね
Are you doing something?
何かやってんの?
I'm overdoing it.
無理無理してる
interesting?
面白い?
Are you acting on your own?
勝手になってんの?
Are you acting like a douche like this without permission?
勝手にこんなドスケで鼻になってんの?
Okay,
よし、
Okay, okay, okay.
よし、 よし、よし
Facing the camera, sideways, sideways, sideways.
カメラに向かって、横に、横に、横に
yes?
そう?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, nice, nice.
そう、そう、そう、いいね、いいね
Hine throws it forward though.
ひねが前に投げるけどね
Okay, come a little closer to the camera.
よし、もうちょっとカメラに寄ってな
Oshiyu also smells really good.
おしゆかもすごいいい匂いするんだよね
Okay, okay, okay.
よし、よし、よし
Okay, okay.
よし、よし、
よし、 よし
Put your face on the bed.
顔をさ、ベッドにつけてこな
Spread your hands over your buttocks.
両手のお尻に広げてこな
Come on, come on, come on.
さあ、さあ、さあ、さあ
Do you want your penis to sleep more?
もっとおちんちん寝てほしい?
Do you want me to sleep?
寝てほしい?
Can you make the cut wider?
もっとカット広げて?
Spread the cut?
カット広げて?
Please tell me to sleep more.
もっと寝てくださいって言ってこな
Okay,
よし、
So, why don't you just try it once, even if you put your hair together?
じゃあ 髪の毛を一緒にしても 一回だけやってみる?
Come on, come on, come on.
さあ、さあ、さあ
Shall I try sleeping?
寝 てみる?
It's a penis bibim.
おちんこビビンだよ
Ah, grass.
あっ、くさ
Doesn't it smell?
臭くない?
odor.
臭い
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
よし、よし、よし、よし、
Okay.
よし
Will you give me a hat for Ureshi-san's chukubichi?
う れしさんのチュクビチって お帽子してもらう?
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
さあ、さあ、さあ、さあ、
here we go.
さ あ
Are you saying please give me a lot?
すげしいっぱいくださいって言ってる?
Uresh-san's smell is amazing. Are you asking me to give you a lot?
うれしさんの臭いすげし いっぱいくださいって言ってる?
Tell me you want more?
もっといっぱいついてって言って?
Ume.
う め
I asked Rinna to cum all over her dirty pussy.
りんなのきたないマン子にいっぱい 出 してくださいって言
Are you saying that?
ってる の?
Tell Rinna's dirty pussy to please give it to me?
りんなのきたないマン子にいっぱい 出してくださいって言って?
Please give it once.
一回だしてください
Are you saying please let Rinna go?
りんなをはらばしてくださいって言ってるの?
Haraba?
はらば?
Do you want me to go?
いってもらう?
Do you want to hold it as you like?
好きに持つように見ます?
yeah?
ん?
Are you saying you'll look at it as you like?
好きに持つように見ますって言ってるの?
Waiting for a dream
夢まって
Youth research and
Please give me as much as you can.
い っぱい出してください
Please say more.
もっと言ってください
も っと言ってください
Please give me a lot.
いっぱい出してください
Please say more.
もっと言ってください
Yeah.
うん
Please tell me your pussy wants you to live or die.
マンコが生死欲しがって、言ってください
What about the pussy?
マンコは?
Can you have legs?
足を持てる?
This is from power.
これが力から
Is it uncomfortable to cut off the bottom?
下を絶たるのが気持ち悪い?
Something...
なんか...
No.
いやだ
Hold on a little longer.
もうちょっと我慢して
Can you put pressure on your butt?
お尻側に力を入れられる?
Ah, nice, nice.
あ、いいねいいね
Please say squeak a few times.
何回かキュッキュッキュって何回か言ってくれ
That's right, that's right.
そうそう そうそう
I'll spread it out.
広げるよ
Doesn't it hurt?
痛くない?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
I'll put a lid on it so it doesn't overflow any further.
これ以上溢れないように蓋をしてあげるね
Yes, I'll cover it.
はい、蓋をしてあげます
See you then, bye.
じゃあね、バイバイ
Did you say while doing peace that you even stood up?
中 立ちさえちゃいましたってピースしながら言ってたの?
I was even neutral.
中立ちさえちゃいました
Yay?
イエーイ?
Yay.
イエーイ
Yes, Rina-chan.
はい、りなちゃん
Let's try putting it inside.
それ、中入れてみようか
Would you like to come in?
入んないか?
It might not come in.
入んないかもしれない
Ah, it's in.
あ、入ってるね
it hurts?
痛い?
Ah, see you then.
あ、じゃあねもう
Let's try our best to the best of our ability.
頑張れるところまで頑張ってみようか
Once you put it in, I want you to hold it there for a while.
入れたらちょっとそこでキープしてほしい
Let's try our best to keep it.
頑張ってキープしてみよう
It hurts, isn't it?
痛いよね
Can you keep it here?
ここでさ、キープできる?
Oh, I guess I'm the one keeping it.
あ、てか俺がキープしてるのが俺
Yeah, yeah, that's what it feels like.
そうそうそう、そんな感じそんな感じ
I'll try my best to get inside.
ちょっと頑張って中を取りますよ
I'm going to cut this one a little bit here as well.
こ っちの方もちょっとこっちで切る
Good, good.
いいねいいね
Wow, it's pure white.
うわー、真っ白ですね
pure white?
真っ白?
Is it white?
白なの?
white.
白
Drink sperm.
精子飲みる
Just move slowly, just a little bit.
ゆっくりだけ、ちょっとだけ動かすよ
it hurts?
痛い?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
This is amazing.
これはすごいな
It's full of folds.
ひだだらけだ
It feels good.
気持ちいいわけだもん
It has a healthy salmon pink color.
健康的なサーモンピンクの色してますよ
Salmon pink?
サーモンピンク?
Yes, it's a healthy pussy.
うん、健康的なおまんこです
Okay, so let's take it out a little bit.
よし、じゃあちょっと抜いてみよう
Well then, Ya-chan, let's try adding that again.
じゃあ、やーちゃんそれちょっとまた入れてみようか
It's like this.
こんな感じですよ
Wow, that's amazing.
え、すげー
I saw it for the first time.
初めて見た
That's amazing, isn't it?
すごいでしょ
Then, you don't have to go to the point where you cut it and then slowly release it.
で、切るところまで行って、そこでゆっくり出し切れなくていい
Please take it in and out slowly.
から、 ゆっくり出し入れしてごらん
Take it out and put it back in.
ちょっと抜いて、また入れて
And then I put it back in and yeah yeah yeah yeah.
で、また入れて、そうそうそうそう
Take it slow.
ゆっくりやってごらん
I'm covered in seshimire.
せしまみれですわ
Okay, so let's take it out slowly.
よし、じゃあゆっくり抜いてみようか
Please open it.
開けてごらん
Yes, thank you very much.
はーい、ありがとうございました
Shall we go take a bath?
お風呂行こうか
Well then, Ya-chan, let's try adding that again.
じゃあ、やーちゃんそれちょっとまた入れてみようか
Ah, I'm in.
あー、入った
It's like this.
こんな感じですよ
Wow, that's amazing.
え、すげー
I saw it for the first time.
初めて見た
That's amazing, isn't it?
すごいでしょ
Then, you don't have to go to the point where you cut it and then slowly release it.
で、切るところまで行って、そこでゆっくり出し切れなくていい
Please take it in and out slowly.
から、 ゆっくり出し入れしてごらん
Take it out and put it back in.
ちょっと抜いて、また入れて
And then I put it back in and yeah yeah yeah yeah.
で、また入れて、そうそうそうそう
So, do it slowly.
で、ゆっくりやってごらん
I'm covered in seshimire.
せしまみれですわ
Okay, so let's take it out slowly.
よし、じゃあゆっくり抜いてみようか
Please open it.
開けてごらん
Yes, thank you very much.
はーい、ありがとうございました
Shall we go take a bath?
お 風 呂行こうか